(Penny:)I'll come up with something
mushy, you'll cry, we got this.
"Penny, we are
made of particles
"that have existed since the
moment the universe began.
"I like to think
those atoms traveled
"14 billion years through
time and space to create us,
(Leonard:)so that we could be together
and make each other whole."
(Amy:)Wow.
(Official:)Penny?
(Penny:)Right. Um... okay.
(chuckles)
(Penny:)Leonard, I mean, you're not
only the love of my life.
(Penny:)I mean,
you're my best friend, and...
(Penny:)...you've got a friend in me.
(Penny:)You got troubles.
(Penny:)I got 'em, too.
(Penny:)There isn't anything
I wouldn't do for you.
(Penny:)We stick together,
and we can see it through,
(Penny:)'cause... you've got
a friend in me.